http://www.pharmiweb.com/legal/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us and this Privacy Policy sets out how we will process your personal data and what rights you have in respect of your own personal data. We will securely store and process personal data which you have provided to us.
Pharmiweb.com / PharmiWeb.jobs are trade websites owned by Pharmiweb 2002 Limited (referred to as “we”, “our” or “us” in this policy)
The aim of this Privacy Policy is to tell you how we will use any personal data we collect or you provide to us. Please read it carefully before you proceed. We want to be open and transparent with you, and therefore encourage you to contact us if you have any questions about this policy or the ways in which we use your personal data.
This policy applies to our Job Board Applicants, business contacts, clients’ and suppliers’ employees and third parties generally. We take our privacy responsibilities seriously and are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.
For the purpose of applicable privacy legislation, the data controller is Pharmiweb 2002 Limited of One Station Square, Bracknell, Berkshire, England RG12 1QB. Our registered company number is 12000217.
Questions regarding this policy should be directed to our Data Protection Compliance Manager who can be contacted at help@pharmiweb.com. The Data Protection Compliance Manager is responsible for ensuring compliance with relevant data protection legislation and with this policy. Any questions about the operation of this policy or any concerns that the policy has not been followed should be referred in the first instance to the Data Protection Compliance Manager.
1. What information do we hold about you?
We may collect, store and use personal data about you (referred to throughout this privacy policy as personal information):
Business contacts
Contact details such as your name, title, telephone number and e-mail address.
Information that you provide or we collect during our interactions with you or your employer, such as how long we have done business with you or how long you have worked at your company.
Clients’ and Suppliers’ Employees
Your contact details such as your name, title, telephone number and email address.
Information that you provide or we collect during our interactions with you or your employer, such as how long we have done business with you or how long you have worked at your company.
Your bank account details where required for invoicing purposes.
Your bank details where you opt to make an online payment which are not retained or stored by us.
Generally
Other personal information you provide to us via our website, for example, by using the “Newsletter Signup” page on our website.
Information gathered when you visit our office.
Any personal information you provide to us during your interactions with us.
Information provided to us by third party service providers we work with, for example, analytics providers.
2. How will we use your personal information and what is the legal ground we rely on for doing so?
We will only use your personal information when the law allows us to. When we use your personal information, we must have a legal ground for doing so. The following are (amongst others) the legal grounds by which we can use your personal information:
Where you have provided us with your consent for us to do so;
Where we need to perform the contract we have entered into with you or to take steps to enter into a contract with you;
Where we need to comply with a legal obligation to which we are subject;
Where it is in pursuit of our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.
More specifically, we will use your personal information in the following circumstances:
Business contacts
Your contact details to provide you with information on our products and services. This may include technical information and/or marketing information – in pursuit of our legitimate interests in keeping you informed about our products, services and business updates.
Your contact details to facilitate business between your company and ours – in pursuit of our legitimate interest of daily business with your company.
Clients’ and Suppliers’ Employees
Your contact details to provide you with information on our products and services. This may include technical information and/or marketing information – in pursuit of our legitimate interests in keeping you informed about our products, services and business updates.
Your contact details and payment details to facilitate business between your company and ours – in pursuit of our legitimate interest of daily business with your company.
Generally
To ensure our premises are kept secure – in pursuit of our legitimate interests (in ensuring our premises are kept secure and to keep evidence of this).
Health and safety purposes – to comply with a legal obligation.
To administer our website and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes – in pursuit of our legitimate interests (to better understand how people interact with our website and solve any issues it may have).
To transfer to third party service providers – in pursuit of our legitimate interests (in outsourcing for effectiveness and efficiency).
To contact you if we wish to use your information for a purpose not set out in this policy – to comply with a legal obligation.
3. What happens if there is a change of purpose?
We will only use your personal information for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If we need to use your personal information for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and we will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so.
4. Which type of third parties might we share your personal information with?
We require third parties to respect the security of your personal information and to treat it in accordance with the law. For example, where we instruct third party service providers, we carry out due diligence on those providers to ensure they treat your personal information as seriously as we do.
We may share your personal information with the following types of third parties:
Technical support providers, for example, assisting with our website including the facilitation of payments.
Security companies testing, monitoring and maintaining IT security systems.
Professional advisers such as lawyers, accountants and business analysts.
Providers which help us collate and organise information effectively and securely.
Providers which assist us with marketing.
Third party software hosting companies which provide us with software solutions.
Providers which host our servers in their data centres.
5. Data retention
How long will we use your personal information for?
We will only retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for.
We assess the appropriate retention period for different information based on the size, volume, nature and sensitivity of that information, the potential risk of harm to you from unauthorised use or disclosure of that information, the purposes for which we are using that information, applicable legal requirements for holding that information, and whether we can achieve those purpose(s) through other means.
Business contacts
The period we keep your personal information depends on a number of circumstances. For example where we have collected your personal information during the course of your and our organisations doing business, we will keep your personal information for as long as this business continues, or for as long as we have a commercial interest in holding your personal information, for example, with a view to doing business in the future.
Clients’ and Suppliers’ Employees
The period we keep your personal information depends on a number of circumstances. For example where we have collected your personal information during the course of your and our organisations doing business, we will keep your personal information for as long as this business continues, or for as long as we have a commercial interest in holding your personal information, for example, with a view to doing business in the future.
We do not store any bank details provided when making payments via our websites..
6. Where we store your personal data
Electronic versions of your personal information are stored on our hosting company’s cloud servers. Any transfers of personal data outside of the European Economic Area (EEA) will be done lawfully.
Where we use third party service providers to assist us, your personal information may also be stored in accordance with their practices and procedures. We require third parties to respect your personal information and to treat it in accordance with the law.
7. Rights of access, correction, erasure and restriction
Your rights in connection with your personal information
Under certain circumstances, by law you have the right to:
Request access to your personal information (known as a “data subject access request”). This enables you to receive a copy of the personal information we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.
Request correction of the personal information that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate information we hold about you corrected.
Request the erasure of your personal information. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal information when there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to stop processing personal information where we are relying on a legitimate interest and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground.
Request the restriction of processing of your personal information. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of personal information about you, for example if you want us to establish its accuracy or the reason for processing it.
Request the transfer of your personal information to another party.
If you want to review, verify, correct or request erasure of your personal information, object to the processing of your personal data, or request that we transfer a copy of your personal information to another party, please contact our Data Protection Compliance Manager in writing using the contact details set out at the beginning of this privacy policy.
In the event that you are a Job Board Applicant, a Recruiter or a contributor, please note that you are able to review, correct the personal data that we hold about you via your online dashboard when you are logged in to our PharmiWeb.com or PharmiWeb.jobs websites.
8. No fee usually required
You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal information (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request for access is clearly unfounded or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with the request in such circumstances.
9. What we may need from you
We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access any personal information (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal information is not disclosed to another person who has no right to receive it.
10. Right to withdraw consent
In the limited circumstances where you may have provided your consent to the collection, processing and transfer of your personal information for a specific purpose, you have the right to withdraw your consent for that specific processing at any time. To withdraw your consent, please contact our Data Protection Compliance Manager in writing using the contact details set out at the beginning of this privacy policy.
Where we are providing you with marketing information, you can also change your marketing preferences by using the unsubscribe button at the bottom of our marketing emails sent to you.
Once we have received notification that you have withdrawn your consent, we will no longer process your personal information for the purpose or purposes you originally agreed to, unless we have another legitimate basis for doing so.
11.    What happens if you fail to provide personal information?
If you fail to provide certain information when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract we have entered into with you (such as providing you with our products or services), or we may be prevented from complying with our legal obligations (such as to ensure the health and safety of visitors to our premises).
12.    Right to complain
You have the right to make a complaint if you wish to do so. The organisation with oversight of our processing is the Information Commissioner’s Office, which can be contacted in writing at Information Commissioner’s Office, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, by telephone (0303 123 1113) or by email (casework@ico.org.uk).
13.    Changes to this privacy policy
We may change, modify, add or remove portions of this policy at any time, and any changes will become effective immediately.
Any changes we make to our privacy policy will be posted on this page and, where possible, notified to you.
You are leaving PharmiWeb.com
Disclaimer: You are now leaving PharmiWeb.com website and are going to a website that is not operated by us. We are not responsible for the content or availability of linked sites.
ABOUT THIRD PARTY LINKS ON OUR SITE
PharmiWeb.com offers links to other third party websites that may be of interest to our website visitors. The links provided in our website are provided solely for your convenience and may assist you in locating other useful information on the Internet. When you click on these links you will leave the PharmiWeb.com website and will be redirected to another site. These sites are not under the control of PharmiWeb.com.
PharmiWeb.com is not responsible for the content of linked third party websites. We are not an agent for these third parties nor do we endorse or guarantee their products. We make no representation or warranty regarding the accuracy of the information contained in the linked sites. We suggest that you always verify the information obtained from linked websites before acting upon this information.
Also, please be aware that the security and privacy policies on these sites may be different than PharmiWeb.com policies, so please read third party privacy and security policies closely.
If you have any questions or concerns about the products and services offered on linked third party websites, please contact the third party directly.
Continue
No, thanks
Home
Partners
Company Directory
Events
Conference
Training
;
